A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1962-1963
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1962-1963
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.661
This collection consists of 18,600 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 14 July 1966.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
Contents List
- General Files, 1962-1963
  - "A - Am" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - "An - Az" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Academic Deans 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Admissions 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Panel on ROTC Affairs 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Air Force and Air Force ROTC 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association 1962-1963 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Chapters Planned (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Atlanta Chapter 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Birmingham Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Charleston, West Virginia (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Charlotte, North Carolina (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Chattanooga Chapter 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Danville Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Lynchburg Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Memphis Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Peninsula Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Philadelphia Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Richmond Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Tidewater Tri-County Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Washington Chapter (Univ. of Va. Club of Washington) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Wilmington Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni - Winchester Chapter (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Fund 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Speeches (see "Speeches") 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - American Association of University Professors 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - American Council on Education 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Annual Reports 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "A" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "B" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "C" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "D" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "E" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "F" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "G" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "H" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "I" (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "J" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "K" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "L" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "M" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "N" (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "O" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "P" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "Q" (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "R" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "S" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "T" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "U" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "V" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "W" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "X - Y - Z" 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Architecture 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Army - General 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Army - Judge Advocate General's (J.A.G.) School 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Army -ROTC 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Art 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Art Commission 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Association of American Colleges 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Association of American Universities 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Astronomy 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Athletics: July - December 1962 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Athletics: January - June 1963 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Athletics - A.C.C. 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - N.C.A.A. 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Invitations to Games; Board of Visitors; State Officials; etc. 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Football: V.M.I. Game, 13 October 1962 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Football: Wake Forest Game - Homecoming, 20 October 1962 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Football: Davidson Game - Band and Chorus Day, 27 October 1962 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Football: North Carolina - Commonwealth Day, 10 November 1962 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - "Ba - Bl" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - "Bo - Bz" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Berkeley, Francis L., Jr. 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Biology 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Biology - Blandy Farm 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Biology - Mountain Lake 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Budget Requests 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds - Planning Department 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - General 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Clinch Valley College (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Copeley Hill 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Field House (see University Hall) (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - George Mason College (see George mason College) (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Life Science Building (see Life Science Building) (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - University Hall (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Bureau of Population and Economic Research 1962-1963 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Bureau of Public Administration 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Bursar 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - "Ca - Ck" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - "Cl - Ca" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Calendar for Deans 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Calendar of Events 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Catholic Center 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Cavalier Daily 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Chancellor for Community Colleges 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Children's Rehabilitation Center 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Civil Defense 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Clinch Valley College 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - Charlottesville 200th Anniversary Commission 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Chemistry Building 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Civic Beautification Program 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Classics 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - College of Arts and Sciences: July - December 1962 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - College of Arts and Sciences: January - June 1963 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Commerce, McIntire School of 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Commission on Public Education (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Commission on State Capital Outlay 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Administrative 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Admissions 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Arboretum Advisory 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Architectural Advisory 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Athletic Advisory 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Calendar of Events (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Calendar and Scheduling 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Catalogue 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Cemetery 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Chapel 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Chemistry Building 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Clinch Valley Advisory 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Clinch Valley Science Building (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Community Colleges 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Community Colleges Building (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Committee - Computer Center 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Contractual Relations (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Special Committee on Deans 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Dormitory 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Dormitory Counselors 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Fellowship Awards 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Field House 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Fine Arts 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Foreign Nationals (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Fraternities 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Graduate Degrees in Summer 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Housing 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Institutional Analysis (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Special Lectures 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Library 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Long-Range Planning 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Married Student Housing (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Master Plan 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Medical Board of Hospital 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Names for Buildings 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Objects of Art 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Orientation 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Page-Barbour and Richard Lectures 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Patrick-Henry Advisory 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Pre-Medical Evaluation 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Processions 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Public Occasions 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Public Relations (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Registration 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Research 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Scholarships, Loans, and Employment 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Special Lectures 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Student Activities 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Student Health 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - University Committee on Students 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Summer Session 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Teacher Education 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Traffic Control (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Tree 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Undergraduates (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - University Press 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - University Records (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - University Union 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Virginia Status of University Students 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Wilson Gee Institute for Research in the Social Sciences 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Clippings 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - College Bowl Scholarship 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Community College Proposed (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Community Development Seminar 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Comptroller 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Computer Center 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Confidential Reports (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Cooper, Weldon 1962-1963 (Box 8)
  - Copeley Hill 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - Council on American Graduate Education (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - Council of Southern Universities (see also Southern Fellowships Fund) 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - Council of Southern Universities Proposal 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - "D" - Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - Darden, C. W., Jr. 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - "E" - Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - Economics 1962-1963 (Box 9)
  - Education 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - Educational Research, Division of 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - Endowment Fund - Alumni Board of Trustees 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - Educational T.V. 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - Engineering: July - December 1962 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - Engineering: January - June 1963 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - English 1962-1963 (Box 10)
  - Enrollment 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - "F" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Faculty 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Administrative Structure 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Departmental Chairmen 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Committees 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Candidates for Deanship 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Orientation Program and Reception 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Minutes 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Faulkner Foundation 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Cross 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - DuPont 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Fulbright 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Love: 1961 - 30 June 1962 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Love: 1962 - 1963 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Rhodes 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Finals 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Food Service 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Ford Foundation (see also Thomas Jefferson Center and Econ.) 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Foreign Affairs 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Foreign Student Advisor 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Founder's Day 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fraternities 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fund for Adult Education (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - General Assembly (see also Legislative Program) 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - General Studies, School of 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - General Studies, School of - re: Hazel Ruth Adams - August - October 1962 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - General Studies - Branches proposed 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - General Studies - Lynchburg 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - General Studies - Madison 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Center (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - General Studies - Patrick Henry Branch 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - General Studies - Roanoke 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - Geology 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - Geography 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - Germanic Languages and Russian (see Modern Languages) 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - Gifts and Grants - July - December 1962 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - Gifts and Grants - January - June 1963 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - Governor's Office 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - Governor's Office - Advices of Allotments 1962-1963 (Box 13)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences - 3-years Masters Program 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - "Ha - Hk" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - "Ho - Hz" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - Highway Department 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - History 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - Honor System 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - Honors Courses 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - Hospital 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Hospital - Rehabilitation Teaching and Training Center (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Housing (see also Housing Committee) 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - "I" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Institute of International Education 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Institutional Analysis, Office of (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Institutional Self-Study (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "A" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "B" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "C" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "D" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "E" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "F" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "G" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "H" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "I" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "J" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "K" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "L" 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "M" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "N" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "O" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "P" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "Q" (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "R" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "S" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "T" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "U" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "V" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "W" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "X- Y- Z" 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson Society 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson, Thomas - Award 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson, Thomas - Center (see also Economics and Ford Foundation) 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson, Thomas - Memorial Foundation 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson, Thomas - Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 17)
  - John Randolph Society 1962-1963 (Box 17)
  - "K" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 17)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 17)
  - Law School 1962-1963 (Box 17)
  - Lectures - General 1962-1963 (Box 17)
  - Legal Matters 1962-1963 (Box 17)
  - Legal - Alderman Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Alley (Grace) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Ambler (Mary O.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Anderson (Dr. John F.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Aunspaugh (Vivan Louise) - Dallas properties 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Bagot (Bernard W. N.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Balch (Emily Clark) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Bayly-Tiffany (see Tiffany Estate) (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Beall (Mattie Brooke) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Biloxi Marsh Land Corporation - Succession of Vincent 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Blackwell (Hugh D.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Brown (Chapman J.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Buchanan (Ward) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Chinn (Mary Scott) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Councill (Malcolm S.) - Trust 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Cranford (Arlette) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Crockett (Nathan A.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Culbreth (Dr. D. M. R.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Curd (William A.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Dunkel Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Fowlkes (E. J.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Griffin (Malcolm) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Henry (Mrs. Bennie B.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Holcombe (Mary L.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Hopkins (William E.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Howard (Nannie Vaughan) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Howze (S. Perry) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Hubert (Conrad) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Humphreys (William Jackson) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Johnson (Mattie L.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Jones (T. Catesby) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Kaprielian (Dr. H. Kruger) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Kehlenbeck (Alfred P.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Kimball (Mrs. mare G.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Kovalenko (Michael S.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Lambert (W. A. and Mrs. Frank Irene Lamberth, his wife) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Lane (Mrs. Emma Gildersleeve) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Langhorne (Cary D.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - La Pierre (Guy M.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Latimer (Anne Mayo) - Trust 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Lehman (Linwood) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Liberian Development Corporation 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Littleton (Henrietta Olive) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - McIntire (Paul G.) - Trust 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - McReynolds (Justice) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Maas (Kittyn M.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Macrae (Richard Moncure) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Makinson (Bertha L.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Mark (Ellie Marcus) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Meaders (Paul L., Jr.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Memminger (Christopher G.) - Trust 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Miller (Kathleen P.) - Trust 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Miller (Lizzie) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Miller (Samuel) - Fund 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Mitchell (Samuel) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Moore (John Bassett) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Morea (Property) 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Moyston (Roy C.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Newcomb (John Lloyd) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Parrish (Harcourt) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Powell (Louise Mathilde) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Pratt (Lilian) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Randall-MacIver Trust 1962-1963 (Box 18)
  - Legal - Rucker (W. J.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Rushton Memorial Fund 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Ryan (Thomas Fortune) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Samuels (Dr. Bernard) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Seay (George J. and Effie L.) -Memorial Trust 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Seward (Walter M.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Shields (Mazyck Wilson) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Sides (Harriet S. R.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Smith (Florence L.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Stanfield (Theodore) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Steele (Boyd Mager) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Taylor (Lillian G.) - Trust 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Thomas (Benjamin F.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Thompson (Mar and Frances) - Trust 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Thurman (Mrs. Charles) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Tiffany (Evelyn May Bayly) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Toole (John) - Memorial Trust 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Vincent (Hugh E.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Watts (Dr. S. H.) - Bequest 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - White (Elizabeth McClung) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - White (Ida E.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Willard (Belle L. W.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Wilson (P. St. Julian) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Woodford (Elizabeth W.) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legal - Young (Claudia Palmer) - Estate 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Legislative Program 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Liberal Arts 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Library 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Library - Board of Alderman 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Life Sciences Building (see Gilmer Hall, 1963-1964) (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Longwood Foundation 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - "M - Me" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 20)
  - "Mi - Mz" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 20)
  - Marine Science 1962-1963 (Box 20)
  - Mary Washington College 1962-1963 (Box 20)
  - Mathematics 1962-1963 (Box 21)
  - Maxwell Air Force Base 1962-1963 (Box 21)
  - Medicine: July - December 1962 1962-1963 (Box 21)
  - Medicine: January - June 1963 1962-1963 (Box 21)
  - Modern Languages 1962-1963 (Box 21)
  - Music 1962-1963 (Box 21)
  - "N" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 21)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (see also Virginia Association Research Center) 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - National Association of State Universities 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - National Commission on Accrediting 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - National Defense Education Act 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - National Science Foundation 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - Navy - General 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - Navy - ROTC 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - Newcomb Hall 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - Newcomen Society 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - Newman Hall (see also Catholic Center) 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - News Letter 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - Nursing 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - Old Dominion Foundation 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - "P - Ph" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - "Pi - Pz" Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Physics 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Personnel (see Police Survey for classification of Security Director) 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Philosophy 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Photographs (folder empty) 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Police Survey (University) 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Political Science 1962-1963 (Box 23)
  - Possible Donors 1962-1963 (Box 24)